

Bernardo de Oliveira Rodrigues

"The life you live is more important than the words you speak."

My name is Bernardo de Oliveira Rodrigues, I have 26 years of age, and I'm currently living in Lisbon, Portugal. I am currently studying for an undergraduate degree in Information Technology Management at ULHT - Universidade Lusófona de Humanidades e Tecnologias.

Competencies >

Driver's license (B and B1) since 16/11/2018 and CMTVDE nº 10210/2019

Education

- 17/09/2010 11/06/2016 Escola Secundária Pedro Nunes, Lisboa, Portugal science and technology program
- 20/09/2019 10/06/2020 Escola Secundária Camões, Lisboa, Portugal Studying to take the national exams
- 15/10/2020 until now ULHT Universidade Lusófona de Humanidades e Tecnologias – Enrolled in a undergraduate degree in Information Technology Management

Work experience

- 01/06/2014 14/08/2014 Shop assistant at Pull & Bear warehouse management and customer service
- 10/10/2014 10/10/2015 Commercial Model at Elite Models (TV commercials)
- 10/11/2018 31/12/2021 Condominium Administrator
- 10/10/2021 01/06/2022 Junior IT Consultant
- 05/06/2020 until now Commercial Model at Estoril Models (TV commercials)
- 01/11/2016 until now Self-employed Driver

Hobbies & Soft skills @

- Photography
- Sports Bodyboard, Boxing and weightlifting
- Technology
- Cooking
- Communication Public speaking and Interpersonal communication

Languages I

- Portuguese (Native Language)
- English Proficient level at listening, reading, spoken interaction and spoken production – reads and speaks English daily
- Spanish Basic level, mostly from interacting with Spanish speaking people

Digital Portfolio

https://bernardorodrigues22007519.github.io/#



Campolide, Lisboa, Portugal



bernardorodrigues2 b@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/bernardo-rodrigues-tob/